cucumbertown.com 2017-03-27

# Privacy Policy | Cucumbertown

_Last Updated – September 25, 2012_

Cucumbertown allows its users, via the Cucumbertown website (http://cucumbertown.com) (the "Website"), to participate in a simple recipe blogging platform allowing amateur cooks to develop devoted followings (collectively, the "Cucumbertown Service"). The Cucumbertown Service is owned and operated by Cucmbertown, Inc., a Delaware corporation ("Cucumbertown", "we" or "us").

Your use of the Website and the Cucumbertown Service is subject to the terms and conditions set forth in this Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy").

 **PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING OR USING OUR WEBSITE OR THE CUCUMBERTOWN SERVICE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND TO ALL THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND OUR WEBSITE TERMS OF SERVICE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS, EXIT THIS PAGE AND DO NOT ACCESS OR USE THE WEBSITE OR THE CUCUMBERTOWN SERVICE.**

We are committed to respect and protect the privacy of the personal information we obtain from you through our Website and we have created this Privacy Policy to inform you about how we collect, use and share your personal information, and our privacy practices in general.

We are always ready to address your questions and concerns regarding this policy and our privacy practices. If you would like to contact Customer Service, please contact us via [privacy@cucumbertown.com](mailto:privacy@cucumbertown.com).

We continually strive to find new ways to enhance your experience with the Website and the Cucumbertown Service and we may modify this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect changes in our privacy practices. You are encouraged to review this Privacy Policy periodically and to check the "Last Updated" date at the top of the Privacy Policy for the most recent version. If we make changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of notice on the Website or otherwise through the Cucumbertown Service.

## 1\. Terms of Service.

Use of the Website and the Cucumbertown Service is subject to the terms of our Terms of Service, which is hereby incorporated into and made part of this Privacy Policy. Please carefully review our Terms of Service. By using the Website or the Cucumbertown Service, you agree to be bound by the terms of our Terms of Service.

## 2\. Types and Uses of Collected Information.

Cucumbertown collects two types of information about you:

  *  **a. Personally Identifiable Information.** Personally Identifiable Information is information that identifies a specific person. When you engage in certain activities on this Website or through your participation in the Cucumbertown Service, including but not limited to creating an account, sending feedback, or otherwise participating in the Cucumbertown Service (collectively, "Identification Activities"), we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself. If you elect to engage in an Identification Activity, however, we may ask you to provide us with certain personal information about yourself, such as your name, address (including zip code), email address, telephone number, and date of birth. When you enroll in the Cucumbertown Service, we may also ask you to provide us with additional information, such as credit card information. Depending on the Identification Activity, some of the information we ask you to provide may be identified as mandatory and some identified as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory information for a particular Identification Activity that requires it, you will not be permitted to engage in that Identification Activity. Depending on the Identification Activity, Cucumbertown may not re-ask you for Personally Identifiable Information if such are already stored with us under the Cucumbertown Service.

If you choose to refer someone through the Cucumbertown Service, we will ask you for your referral's contact information, such as his or her name and email address. We may then send your friend an email inviting him or her to visit the Website and/or join the Cucumbertown Service. Cucumbertown stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this email and maintaining the Cucumbertown Service. Your friend may contact us at [privacy@cucumbertown.com](mailto:privacy@cucumbertown.com) to request that we remove his or her contact information from our records.

We may use Personally Identifiable Information to provide products and/or services to you, administer sweepstakes and contests, enhance the operation of the Website and the Cucumbertown Service, improve our marketing and promotional efforts, analyze Website and Cucumbertown Service use, improve the Website and the Cucumbertown Service, and to tailor your experience with third parties as provided below in this Privacy Policy. If you use our Website or the Cucumbertown Service to send information to another person, we may store your personal information. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to troubleshoot, resolve disputes, accomplish administrative tasks, contact you, enforce our agreements with you, including our Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy, comply with applicable law, and cooperate with law enforcement activities.

  *  **b. Non-Personally Identifiable Information.** Non-Personally Identifiable Information is information that does not identify a specific person. This type of information may include things like the Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") of the website you visited before coming to our Website or otherwise participating in the Cucumbertown Service, the URL of the website you visit after leaving our Website or the Cucumbertown Service, the type of browser you are using, your Internet Protocol ("IP") address, or general and/or aggregated location data that does constitute Personally Identifiable Information. We, and/or our authorized Third Party Service Providers and Advertisers, may automatically collect this information when you visit our Website or use the Cucumbertown Service through the use of electronic tools like Cookies and Web beacons or Pixel tags, as described below in this Privacy Policy.

We use Non-Personally Identifiable Information to troubleshoot, administer the Website and the Cucumbertown Service, analyze trends, gather demographic information, comply with applicable law, and cooperate with law enforcement activities. We may also share this information with our authorized Third Party Service Providers and Advertisers to measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, and programming.

## 2\. Release of Personally Identifiable Information.

We will not sell or share your Personally Identifiable Information with other parties except as provided below:

  *  **a. Authorized Third Party Service Providers.** Cucumbertown may provide services and products through third parties. These "Third Party Service Providers" perform functions on our or your behalf. You or We may share your Personally Identifiable Information with such Service Providers to fulfill orders, move data in or out of the Cucumbertown Service, analyze data, provide marketing assistance, provide search results and links, operate the Website and the Cucumbertown Service, troubleshoot, and provide customer service. We may also collect personal information from individuals and companies ("Affiliates") with whom we have business relationships and may share your information with Third Party Service Providers to accomplish our administrative tasks. We encourage Affiliates and Third Party Service Providers to adopt and post privacy policies. However, the use of your Personally Identifiable Information by such parties is governed by the privacy policies of such parties and is not subject to our control.
  *  **b. Remarketing.** Remarketing is a way for Cucumbertown to connect with people, based upon your past interactions with the Website and/or the Cucumbertown Service. Third-party marketing vendors may be hired by Cucumbertown to perform remarketing services. As a result, third-party vendors, including Google, may show Cucumbertown ads on sites on the Internet. Third-party vendors may use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to the Website. Users may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>. Users may opt out of Gourmet Ads’ use of cookies by visiting the opt-out page at <http://www.gourmetads.com/about/privacy-policy>
  * **c. Acquisition.** As with any other company, we could merge with, or be acquired by another company. If this occurs, the successor company would acquire the information we maintain, including Personally Identifiable Information. However, Personally Identifiable Information would remain subject to this Privacy Policy.
  *  **d. As required by law.** We reserve the right to disclose your Personally Identifiable Information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Website; enforce or apply this Privacy Policy, Terms of Service or other agreements; or protect the rights, property or safety of the Website, users of the Cucumbertown Service, employers, or others.

## 3\. Release of Non-Personally Identifiable Information.

We may disclose or share Non-Personally Identifiable Information with Affiliates and Third Party Service Providers, and Third Party Advertisers. For example, we may share aggregated demographic information (which does not include any Personally Identifiable Information) with "Third Party Advertisers" or "Third Party Advertising Companies."

We may use Third Party Advertising Companies to serve ads when you visit our Website or participate in the Cucumbertown Service. These companies may use Non-Personally Identifiable Information about your visits to this Website, your use of the Cucumbertown Service, and visits to other websites or locations in order to provide, through the use of network tags, advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

We also use Third Party Service Providers to track and analyze Non-Personally Identifiable usage and volume statistical information from our users to administer our Website and the Cucumbertown Service, in order to constantly improve their quality. We may also publish this information for promotional purposes or as a representative audience for Third Party Advertisers. Such data is collected on our behalf, and is owned and used by Cucumbertown.

## 4\. Updating Information.

If you are enrolled in the Cucumbertown Service, you may change any of your Personally Identifiable Information by logging into your account and accessing the Profile Settings or by sending us an email at [privacy@cucumbertown.com](mailto:privacy@cucumbertown.com).

We encourage you to promptly update your Personally Identifiable Information if it changes, as out-of-date Personally Identifiable Information may negatively affect the quality of your Cucumbertown Service use and experience. You may ask to have the information on your account deleted or removed; however, because we keep track of past transactions, you cannot delete information associated with past transactions on the Website or through the Cucumbertown Service. Additionally, it may be impossible for us to completely delete all of your information because we periodically backup information.

## 5\. Choices on Collection/Use of Information.

You can always choose not to provide certain information, although a certain level of information is required to engage in activities on the Website and to participate in the Cucumbertown Service.

You cannot opt-out of Administrative Emails. "Administrative Emails" relate to a your activity on the Website and the Cucumbertown Service, and include but are not limited to emails regarding a your account, requests or inquiries, and purchases of products and services. If you do not want to receive promotional emails from us, you may elect to opt-out of receiving promotional emails at any time after registering by e-mailing us at [privacy@cucumbertown.com](mailto:privacy@cucumbertown.com), or by hitting the "unsubscribe" button at the bottom of any of our e-mails.

## 6\. Security of Information.

You can access your Personally Identifiable Information on our Website with your password and username. This password is encrypted. We advise against sharing your password with anyone. In addition, your Personally Identifiable Information resides on a secure server that only selected personnel and contractors have access to. We may encrypt certain sensitive information using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to ensure that your Personally Identifiable Information is safe as it is transmitted to us.

However, no data transmission can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we employ commercially reasonable security measures to protect data and seek to partner with companies that do the same, we cannot guarantee the security of any information transmitted to or from the Website or via the Cucumbertown Service, and are not responsible for the actions of any third parties that may receive any such information.

## 7\. Data Tracking

  *  **a. Cookies.** To facilitate and customize your experience with the Website and the Cucumbertown Service, we may store cookies on your computer or other similar device through which you access the Website or Cucumbertown Service. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your computer or other device for record-keeping purposes which contains information about you. We use cookies to save you time while using the Website and the Cucumbertown Service, remind us who you are, and track and target your interests in order to provide a customized experience. Cookies also allow us to collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information from you, like which pages you visited, what links you clicked on, and how you used the Cucumbertown Service. We may use Third Party Advertising Companies to display advertisements on our Website. As part of their service, they may place separate cookies on your computer or similar device. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by our Website and the Cucumbertown Service only and does not cover the use of cookies by any Advertiser. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, however you may be able to modify your browser settings to decline cookies. Please note that if you decline or delete these cookies, some parts of the Website or the Cucumbertown Service may not work properly.
  *  **b. Other Tracking Devices.** We may use other industry standard technologies like pixel tags and web beacons to track your use of our Website pages and promotions, or we may allow our Third Party Service Providers to use these devices on our behalf. Pixel tags and web beacons are tiny graphic images placed on certain pages on our Website, or in our emails that allow us to determine whether you have performed a specific action. When you access these pages or open or click an email, pixel tags and web beacons generate a Non-Personally Identifiable notice of that action. Pixel tags allow us to measure and improve our understanding of visitor traffic and behavior on our Website, as well as give us a way to measure our promotions and performance. We may also utilize pixel tags and web beacons provided by our Affiliates and/or marketing partners for the same purposes.

## 8\. Privacy Policies of Third Party Websites.

This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you on [http://cucumbertown.com](http://cucumbertown.com/) and via the Cucumbertown Service. Other websites or services that may be accessible through this Website or the Cucumbertown Service may have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. If you luse, link or visit any such website, we urge you review the website's privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties.

## 9\. Privacy Settings.

As a user, you may have limited access to privacy settings. These settings help hide information you wish to share with other users and/or the public. It is up to you to select the appropriate privacy settings. If you don't agree with the available privacy settings, please stop using the Website and the Cucumbertown Service.

## 10\. Public Areas.

We may provide areas on our Website or via the Cucumbertown Service where you can publicly post information about yourself including your location, can communicate with others such as discussion boards, chat rooms, or blogs. This information may be accessible by other users and companies and may appear on other websites or web searches, and therefore this information could be read, collected, and used by others. We have no control over who reads your postings or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post, so please use caution when posting any content or providing anything that could be deemed personal information.

## 11\. Facebook.

The Website or Cucumbertown Service may allow you to access Facebook to interact with friends and to share on Facebook through your or your friends' "Walls" and "News Feeds." By doing so, you agree to allow the Cucumbertown Service to access your information and you are agreeing to the Facebook Terms of Use in your use of the Cucumbertown Service. If you are not currently enrolled in the Cucumbertown Service and you click on "Sign in Using Facebook," you will first be asked to enter your Facebook credentials and then be given the option to register and join the Cucumbertown Service.

## 12\. Notice of Privacy Rights to California Residents.

California law requires that we provide you with a summary of your privacy rights under the California Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA") and the California Business and Professions Code. As required by COPPA, we will provide you with the categories of Personally Identifiable Information that we collect through the Website and the categories of third party persons or entities with whom such Personally Identifiable Information may be shared for direct marketing purposes at your request. California law requires us to inform you, at your request, (1) the categories of Personally Identifiable Information we collect and what third parties we share that information with; (2) the names and addresses of those third parties; and (3) examples of the products marketed by those companies. COPPA further requires us to allow you to control who you do not want us to share that information with. To obtain this information, please send a request by email or physical mail to the address found below. When contacting us, please indicate your name, address, email address, and what Personally Identifiable Information you do not want us to share with Affiliates or marketing partners. The request should be sent to the attention of our legal department, and labeled "California Customer Choice Notice." Please allow 30 days for a response. Also, please note that there is no charge for controlling the sharing of your Personally Identifiable Information or requesting this notice.

## 13\. Children.

The Website and the Cucumbertown Service are not directed to people under 13. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us at [privacy@cucumbertown.com](mailto:privacy@cucumbertown.com). If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account.

## 14\. Customer Service.

For assistance or questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the Cucumbertown Service, you may email us at [privacy@cucumbertown.com](mailto:privacy@cucumbertown.com).
